<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-GB"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-GB" /><updated>2021-07-08T23:41:55+01:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blog.thisispaddys.space</title><subtitle></subtitle><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><entry><title type="html">Why am I doing this?</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/08/why-am-i-doing-this/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why am I doing this?" /><published>2021-07-08T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-08T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/08/why-am-i-doing-this</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/08/why-am-i-doing-this/">&lt;p&gt;I’m a nobody. I guess we all are at some point in our lives. Maybe. Or maybe it’s just me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m on all the usual social media sites under a different username. Got a few acquaintances and people that could be called friends following me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why have I hit the reset button? Started from scratch. Where nobody will read this. Nobody will follow me. I’m not a social person by nature. I don’t have any words of wisdom or skills to offer the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A fifty something&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vegan (non pushy)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;With depression&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Someone who likes the idea of friends. But doesn’t like people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why the hell would I want to attract people to read my very inarticulate blog, look at my mundane pictures or talk to a depressing introvert?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I’m trying to find myself again. I used to have a blogger blog back in the dark ages, and a livejournal and a Tumblr. I recently migrated my old blogger posts to this blog. It was interesting going over them again. Like finding an old diary. I enjoyed being on blogger until I didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I just need this right now. A fresh start. Just a new me on the internet. Where nobody knows me. And maybe nobody will want to know me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I’m ok with that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">I’m a nobody. I guess we all are at some point in our lives. Maybe. Or maybe it’s just me. I’m on all the usual social media sites under a different username. Got a few acquaintances and people that could be called friends following me. So why have I hit the reset button? Started from scratch. Where nobody will read this. Nobody will follow me. I’m not a social person by nature. I don’t have any words of wisdom or skills to offer the world. I’m A fifty something Vegan (non pushy) With depression Someone who likes the idea of friends. But doesn’t like people. So why the hell would I want to attract people to read my very inarticulate blog, look at my mundane pictures or talk to a depressing introvert? I think I’m trying to find myself again. I used to have a blogger blog back in the dark ages, and a livejournal and a Tumblr. I recently migrated my old blogger posts to this blog. It was interesting going over them again. Like finding an old diary. I enjoyed being on blogger until I didn’t. Maybe I just need this right now. A fresh start. Just a new me on the internet. Where nobody knows me. And maybe nobody will want to know me. And I’m ok with that.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A day in my life</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/06/i-hate-time/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A day in my life" /><published>2021-07-06T02:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-06T02:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/06/i-hate-time</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/06/i-hate-time/">&lt;p&gt;3 am Little G wakes me up to go out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6 am My alarm goes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:10 am my alarm goes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:20 am my alarm goes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:30 am my alarm goes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7-8 am I try and survive the morning cat feed, preparing my lunch, getting breakfast. And make a half hearted attempt to be ready and at work for 8 am&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:10 am arrive at work&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:10 am-4:30 pm spend the day in my own pit of hell having to work with some of the dumbest people I have ever had the misfortune of meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:30-8:30 pm This could go either way. Depending on the kind of day Zara has had will dictate everything, from the mood of the cats to affecting every ounce of my being. Watch tv, eat dinner, feed cats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:30-10 pm This will be stressful regardless. Getting cats sorted, fed, and happy whilst we bicker about everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10-12pm Bed. Peace. Quiet. The time I can do what I want, watch what I want. The world has gone to sleep. The world is silent. I should be going to sleep. Getting rest to repeat the whole process all over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I feel my time is wasted being asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I sleep it will be tomorrow even quicker.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">3 am Little G wakes me up to go out. 6 am My alarm goes off. 6:10 am my alarm goes off. 6:20 am my alarm goes off. 6:30 am my alarm goes off. 7-8 am I try and survive the morning cat feed, preparing my lunch, getting breakfast. And make a half hearted attempt to be ready and at work for 8 am 8:10 am arrive at work 8:10 am-4:30 pm spend the day in my own pit of hell having to work with some of the dumbest people I have ever had the misfortune of meeting. 4:30-8:30 pm This could go either way. Depending on the kind of day Zara has had will dictate everything, from the mood of the cats to affecting every ounce of my being. Watch tv, eat dinner, feed cats. 8:30-10 pm This will be stressful regardless. Getting cats sorted, fed, and happy whilst we bicker about everything. 10-12pm Bed. Peace. Quiet. The time I can do what I want, watch what I want. The world has gone to sleep. The world is silent. I should be going to sleep. Getting rest to repeat the whole process all over again. But I feel my time is wasted being asleep. If I sleep it will be tomorrow even quicker.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">I don’t like Mondays</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/05/i-don-t-like-mondays/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I don’t like Mondays" /><published>2021-07-05T07:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-05T07:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/05/i-don-t-like-mondays</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/05/i-don-t-like-mondays/">&lt;p&gt;It’s that feeling of “here we go again” We’re at the top of the rollercoaster. Just bracing for the sudden stomach-churning descent. Which is great if you like the exhilaration of the ride. I’ve always hated rollercoasters. Never been on one. Never wanted to. Never will. Rollercoasters are like life. I never asked to be on the damn thing. But here I am, going through the same stomach-churning experience. Round and round. Up and down. Feeling sicker and sicker as time goes by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to get off. But I’m stuck on this damn thing because everybody I love is here with me. Going through various feelings of exhilaration and nausea of their own. And feeling like, “well, they’re here with me so I’d better stay on the ride”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do sometimes enjoy it. When it’s going slow, at the bottom where it feels like it’s virtually stopped. The calm before the storm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yeah. I don’t like Mondays. Or rollercoasters.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">It’s that feeling of “here we go again” We’re at the top of the rollercoaster. Just bracing for the sudden stomach-churning descent. Which is great if you like the exhilaration of the ride. I’ve always hated rollercoasters. Never been on one. Never wanted to. Never will. Rollercoasters are like life. I never asked to be on the damn thing. But here I am, going through the same stomach-churning experience. Round and round. Up and down. Feeling sicker and sicker as time goes by. I want to get off. But I’m stuck on this damn thing because everybody I love is here with me. Going through various feelings of exhilaration and nausea of their own. And feeling like, “well, they’re here with me so I’d better stay on the ride” I do sometimes enjoy it. When it’s going slow, at the bottom where it feels like it’s virtually stopped. The calm before the storm. So yeah. I don’t like Mondays. Or rollercoasters.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">It’s Caturday</title><link href="/caturday/2021/07/03/its-caturday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It’s Caturday" /><published>2021-07-03T06:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-03T06:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/caturday/2021/07/03/its-caturday</id><content type="html" xml:base="/caturday/2021/07/03/its-caturday/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/e_oil_paint:25/v1625262596/blog/hzwjmcjg1c7zc4lga1vr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Caturday" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The testing is over</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/01/the-testing-is-over/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The testing is over" /><published>2021-07-01T04:01:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-01T04:01:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/01/the-testing-is-over</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/01/the-testing-is-over/">&lt;p&gt;Well. Here I go. A blog about my thoughts and ideas. I don’t have many thoughts. Or ideas. I feel like I just float through life being buffeted by whatever comes my way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember being asked by the careers counselor at school what I wanted to be in life. I didn’t have a clue. I was a suicidal 15 year old so I just said I wanted to be happy. I was asked again when I was at college.  &lt;!-- more --&gt; now a suicidal 17 year old. I still didn’t know. I didn’t know at 20, 30 or 40. I’m now 51 and I still don’t know. Nor do I care now. I’ve sailed through life without any goal or vision. I’ve seen people i love die before their time. I’ve seen relationships crumble and dreams shatter. So I just keep floating through life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1625159510/blog/undraw_career_progress_ivdb_vk9nxw.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Career progress&quot; /&gt;I’ve made half hearted attempts at life. I’ve had moments where things seemed to be going well_._ But they fade away eventually. I’ve been good, bad, selfish, selfless and on occasions illegal. But nothing seems to stick. I’ve thrown myself into interests 110% but eventually the bubble bursts and I’m looking for the next hook. The next thing I can cling onto in the hope it can catapult me through the rest of my life. It’s a lot to ask of something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all sounds so pointless as a life. We’ve only got one life so live it. So they say. But it’s like being given a book and told to read it. And enjoy it. It’s the only book you’re ever going to have. So make the most of it. So you slog your way through page after page of mundane story. Just hoping you can get through it quickly. To get to the end and breathe your last sigh of relief that it’s finally over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">Well. Here I go. A blog about my thoughts and ideas. I don’t have many thoughts. Or ideas. I feel like I just float through life being buffeted by whatever comes my way. I remember being asked by the careers counselor at school what I wanted to be in life. I didn’t have a clue. I was a suicidal 15 year old so I just said I wanted to be happy. I was asked again when I was at college.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Lets Try Again</title><link href="/test/2021/06/30/lets-try-again/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lets Try Again" /><published>2021-06-30T08:19:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-06-30T08:19:00+01:00</updated><id>/test/2021/06/30/lets-try-again</id><content type="html" xml:base="/test/2021/06/30/lets-try-again/">&lt;p&gt;Ok. I think i’ve got the hang of this now. I think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1624693694/undraw_work_in_progress_uhmv_ulcbyg.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s getting there slowly. Hopefully, this will be the last test and I’ll have to start writing something!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Test" /><summary type="html">Ok. I think i’ve got the hang of this now. I think. It’s getting there slowly. Hopefully, this will be the last test and I’ll have to start writing something!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">First Test</title><link href="/test/2021/06/27/first-test/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Test" /><published>2021-06-27T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-06-27T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/test/2021/06/27/first-test</id><content type="html" xml:base="/test/2021/06/27/first-test/">&lt;p&gt;Ok, this is the first test post. Hopefully I won’t have to do this too often,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1624693716/me.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Me&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Test" /><summary type="html">Ok, this is the first test post. Hopefully I won’t have to do this too often,</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Helping hand</title><link href="/website/projects/2012/04/24/helping-hand/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Helping hand" /><published>2012-04-24T17:05:00+01:00</published><updated>2012-04-24T17:05:00+01:00</updated><id>/website/projects/2012/04/24/helping-hand</id><content type="html" xml:base="/website/projects/2012/04/24/helping-hand/">&lt;p&gt;Ok. &lt;del&gt;I said this blog is dead. And so it it. Well, maybe just resting&lt;/del&gt;. Helping my dads local flying club get its new domain off the ground (ahaha) so thought I would try adding a backlink here. So here it is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flyatfranks.org/&quot;&gt;https://www.flyatfranks.org/&lt;/a&gt; If you’re in the lincolnshire area and feel like taking a trial flight to see what your house looks like from the air then check them out. Details of trial flights can be found here &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flyatfranks.org/trial-flight/&quot;&gt;https://www.flyatfranks.org/trial-flight/&lt;/a&gt; There. I`ve done my bit. This totally reads like a spam advert but it’s not :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Paddy</name></author><category term="website" /><category term="projects" /><summary type="html">Ok. I said this blog is dead. And so it it. Well, maybe just resting. Helping my dads local flying club get its new domain off the ground (ahaha) so thought I would try adding a backlink here. So here it is https://www.flyatfranks.org/ If you’re in the lincolnshire area and feel like taking a trial flight to see what your house looks like from the air then check them out. Details of trial flights can be found here https://www.flyatfranks.org/trial-flight/ There. I`ve done my bit. This totally reads like a spam advert but it’s not :)</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sunset</title><link href="/new/york/2011/11/13/sunset/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sunset" /><published>2011-11-13T17:41:00+00:00</published><updated>2011-11-13T17:41:00+00:00</updated><id>/new/york/2011/11/13/sunset</id><content type="html" xml:base="/new/york/2011/11/13/sunset/">&lt;p&gt;As the sun sets on the last day off our holiday, I feel a little
nostalgic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have the post holiday blues, the feeling that the past 2 weeks were all a dream. That reality that normal work life is fast approaching is sending all my holiday memories to the filing cabinet in my brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing currently stopping me from believing that this was all the dream is the 1215 photos currently downloading to the computer! And believe it or not those are supposed to be the cream of the crop from just over 3000 I actually took in total! I think I may have to preen a bit further!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All that is left to say that it really has been an amazing adventure.
I’ve met some great people, seen some magnificent sights and the food,
well, what can I say….. I don’t think anything will taste as good
ever again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within myself I feel a change. I’m a little stronger, a lot wiser and I
have a sense of confidence that I can do things on my own without
‘adult supervision’!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will miss New York and hope one day to return. It really has been a
remarkable experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m hoping to leave this post with a photo of an image that will be
etched in my mind forever. A beautiful ending to a wonderful holiday.
The sunset on the statue of liberty from battery park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bye Bye New York, missing you already! x&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="New" /><category term="York" /><summary type="html">As the sun sets on the last day off our holiday, I feel a little nostalgic. I have the post holiday blues, the feeling that the past 2 weeks were all a dream. That reality that normal work life is fast approaching is sending all my holiday memories to the filing cabinet in my brain. The only thing currently stopping me from believing that this was all the dream is the 1215 photos currently downloading to the computer! And believe it or not those are supposed to be the cream of the crop from just over 3000 I actually took in total! I think I may have to preen a bit further! All that is left to say that it really has been an amazing adventure. I’ve met some great people, seen some magnificent sights and the food, well, what can I say….. I don’t think anything will taste as good ever again! Within myself I feel a change. I’m a little stronger, a lot wiser and I have a sense of confidence that I can do things on my own without ‘adult supervision’! I will miss New York and hope one day to return. It really has been a remarkable experience. I’m hoping to leave this post with a photo of an image that will be etched in my mind forever. A beautiful ending to a wonderful holiday. The sunset on the statue of liberty from battery park. Bye Bye New York, missing you already! x</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Homeward bound</title><link href="/newyork/2011/11/11/homeward-bound/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Homeward bound" /><published>2011-11-11T12:14:00+00:00</published><updated>2011-11-11T12:14:00+00:00</updated><id>/newyork/2011/11/11/homeward-bound</id><content type="html" xml:base="/newyork/2011/11/11/homeward-bound/">&lt;p&gt;We’ve made it as far as Dublin. It’s 8:40am and our bodies are telling
us we should be asleep as its 3:40am!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://lh4.ggpht.com/-_rVSdmwt20g/Tr0Rmc5ZExI/AAAAAAAACUM/Ss9dYq9OeAY/IMAG0622.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Paddy</name></author><category term="NewYork" /><summary type="html">We’ve made it as far as Dublin. It’s 8:40am and our bodies are telling us we should be asleep as its 3:40am!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>