<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-GB"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-GB" /><updated>2021-08-04T05:51:53+01:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blog.thisispaddys.space</title><subtitle>Home</subtitle><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><entry><title type="html">Discworld Cake Tuesday</title><link href="/cakes/2021/08/03/discworld-cake-tuesday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Discworld Cake Tuesday" /><published>2021-08-03T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-03T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/cakes/2021/08/03/discworld-cake-tuesday</id><content type="html" xml:base="/cakes/2021/08/03/discworld-cake-tuesday/">&lt;p&gt;Since the age of 16 when a college friend thrust a well read book into my hand and told me to read it saying&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’ve got to read this. Death is in it, and he turns up with cocktail sticks”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been hooked on the late great &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.terrypratchettbooks.com/&quot; title=&quot;Terry Pratchett&quot;&gt;Terry Pratchett&lt;/a&gt;’s Discworld. The obsession has wained slightly over the years. I’ve read the books, listened to the audiobooks, and watched the TV adaptations*( the only exception being the watch which is an abomination unto Nuggen) that it’s just a part of my DNA. I don’t feel the need to consume the media as obsessively as I did. But every time I think about the Discworld it makes me smile with wonderful memories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like this one! What a fantastic segway into this cake Tuesday offering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627983722/2004_0319Image0062_1_h6adnq.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mother who is equally as enthralled in the Discworld received this lovely creation for her birthday many years ago. I still think it’s her favourite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627983722/2004_0324Image0066_yc04bf.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture quality may not be the best. I might try and dig out some better photos if they exist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are other Discworld cakes that will appear along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The original post for this cake can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2006/07/25/cake-tuesday_25/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="cakes" /><summary type="html">Since the age of 16 when a college friend thrust a well read book into my hand and told me to read it saying “You’ve got to read this. Death is in it, and he turns up with cocktail sticks” I’ve been hooked on the late great Terry Pratchett’s Discworld. The obsession has wained slightly over the years. I’ve read the books, listened to the audiobooks, and watched the TV adaptations*( the only exception being the watch which is an abomination unto Nuggen) that it’s just a part of my DNA. I don’t feel the need to consume the media as obsessively as I did. But every time I think about the Discworld it makes me smile with wonderful memories. Like this one! What a fantastic segway into this cake Tuesday offering. My mother who is equally as enthralled in the Discworld received this lovely creation for her birthday many years ago. I still think it’s her favourite. The picture quality may not be the best. I might try and dig out some better photos if they exist. There are other Discworld cakes that will appear along the way. The original post for this cake can be found here.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Top Terry Pratchett Caturday Quotes</title><link href="/caturday/2021/07/31/top-terry-pratchett-caturday-quotes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top Terry Pratchett Caturday Quotes" /><published>2021-07-31T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-31T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/caturday/2021/07/31/top-terry-pratchett-caturday-quotes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/caturday/2021/07/31/top-terry-pratchett-caturday-quotes/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;favourite-quotes&quot;&gt;Favourite quotes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a few of my favourite cat-related quotes from my favourite author. The late, great &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.terrypratchettbooks.com/&quot; title=&quot;Sir Terry Pratchett&quot;&gt;Sir Terry Pratchett&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627672791/quotes/pratchett-cat-quote-0_ofvinm.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;The cat wonderfully posing in the pictures is Sam.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627672796/quotes/pratchett-cat-quote-1_llilsm.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;Sam actually lived 10 houses down from us. But decided to move in with his brother.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627672802/quotes/pratchett-cat-quote-2_tfpz7m.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;We eventually found out where he lived.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627672808/quotes/pratchett-cat-quote-3_hpsxrj.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;He moved back home, whilst his brother stayed with us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;honorable-mentions&quot;&gt;Honorable Mentions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Assassin moved quietly from roof to roof until he was well away from the excitement around the Watch House. His movements could be called cat-like, except that he did not stop to spray urine up against things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s an interesting fact that fewer than 17 % of Real cats end their lives with the same name they started with. Much family effort goes into selecting one at the start (“She looks like a Winnifred to me”), and then as the years roll by it suddenly finds itself being called Meepo or Ratbag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate cats.” Death’s face became a little stiffer, if that were possible. The blue glow in his eye sockets flickered red for an instant. “I SEE,” he said. The tone suggested that death was too good for cat haters.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="caturday" /><summary type="html">Favourite quotes Just a few of my favourite cat-related quotes from my favourite author. The late, great Sir Terry Pratchett. The cat wonderfully posing in the pictures is Sam. Sam actually lived 10 houses down from us. But decided to move in with his brother. We eventually found out where he lived. He moved back home, whilst his brother stayed with us. Honorable Mentions The Assassin moved quietly from roof to roof until he was well away from the excitement around the Watch House. His movements could be called cat-like, except that he did not stop to spray urine up against things. It’s an interesting fact that fewer than 17 % of Real cats end their lives with the same name they started with. Much family effort goes into selecting one at the start (“She looks like a Winnifred to me”), and then as the years roll by it suddenly finds itself being called Meepo or Ratbag. I hate cats.” Death’s face became a little stiffer, if that were possible. The blue glow in his eye sockets flickered red for an instant. “I SEE,” he said. The tone suggested that death was too good for cat haters.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">I’ve Tried Nothing And I’m All Out Of Ideas</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/29/i-ve-tried-nothing-and-i-m-all-out-of-ideas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I’ve Tried Nothing And I’m All Out Of Ideas" /><published>2021-07-29T06:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-29T06:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/29/i-ve-tried-nothing-and-i-m-all-out-of-ideas</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/29/i-ve-tried-nothing-and-i-m-all-out-of-ideas/">&lt;p&gt;It’s been a month. Already? I know! Time flies when you’re having fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627508807/canva_assets/i_ve_tried_nothing_frqray.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of Pinterest pins claiming to double your page views. Help you start making \(\) in as revenue. Become Master of the Universe in 3 easy steps is ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never expected to make a penny from blogging. And so far my predictions have been correct. I have nothing to say. No pearls of wisdom. Nothing that hasn’t been said a thousand times before. And probably better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why do it? I’m not a social butterfly. I don’t know a ton of people. I’m shy, introverted, and quiet So why do I put myself out there?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-my-niche-again&quot;&gt;what’s My Niche Again?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, really, why? I’d love to know because I’ll be buggered if I know! The online gurus say to find your niche. I have no idea if I have a niche.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I have depression.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I like animals (friends, not food).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I watch tennis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’ve started to go to the gym (which is way, way out of my comfort zone)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’ve tried learning Japanese but I have a terrible memory.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I fall in and out of interests.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I dwell on the negative instead of embracing the positive.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I barely know my own mind sometimes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627506419/illustrations/4443395_p3lfqo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to play around with new things. New services. New websites. It distracts me from the real world. It’s the creation of something. It may be a boring old blog post that offers zero information or entertainment. But I guess it is just. Fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playing around on canva creating crappy graphics. Signing up on form-building sites that nobody will fill out. Looking at pitiful analytics of visitor counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s all just fun. I like to make websites. Nobody will see them. Maybe that’s what I’m missing. I’m just doing this for enjoyment. Probably only me and my other half will ever read this and comment. Maybe my mum too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to go running. I’m never going to be an Olympic athlete. So why do it? Sheer enjoyment. Although with running it doesn’t usually feel like it at the time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an online world where everybody wants to be the best, earn the most. Get the most likes, page views, comments. Be noticed. I guess doing something for self-satisfaction feels a little strange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But maybe, that’s just me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh. So what have I learned?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well for one. I don’t need to quickly write a blog post, half-arse it, and say pretty much nothing interesting. Just to write ‘something’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also rather than being a small fish in a very big pond. I’m more of a speck of dust floating in the universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t expect to be even noticed. You may get a few visitors, who then quickly click to something more interesting.  Hell, I’ve done it myself. Clicked on something, read it, moved on. So I’m just as guilty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Write because you enjoy it. It’s therapeutic. Write for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re not going to make $$$ a month. You’ll be frustrated trying and lose the enjoyment of blogging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a pity post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More of, say, a reality check. A long rambling reality check that has a crappy ending.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="personal" /><summary type="html">It’s been a month. Already? I know! Time flies when you’re having fun. The number of Pinterest pins claiming to double your page views. Help you start making \(\) in as revenue. Become Master of the Universe in 3 easy steps is ridiculous. I never expected to make a penny from blogging. And so far my predictions have been correct. I have nothing to say. No pearls of wisdom. Nothing that hasn’t been said a thousand times before. And probably better. So why do it? I’m not a social butterfly. I don’t know a ton of people. I’m shy, introverted, and quiet So why do I put myself out there? what’s My Niche Again? No, really, why? I’d love to know because I’ll be buggered if I know! The online gurus say to find your niche. I have no idea if I have a niche. I have depression. I like animals (friends, not food). I watch tennis. I’ve started to go to the gym (which is way, way out of my comfort zone) I’ve tried learning Japanese but I have a terrible memory. I fall in and out of interests. I dwell on the negative instead of embracing the positive. I barely know my own mind sometimes. But. I like to play around with new things. New services. New websites. It distracts me from the real world. It’s the creation of something. It may be a boring old blog post that offers zero information or entertainment. But I guess it is just. Fun. Playing around on canva creating crappy graphics. Signing up on form-building sites that nobody will fill out. Looking at pitiful analytics of visitor counts. It’s all just fun. I like to make websites. Nobody will see them. Maybe that’s what I’m missing. I’m just doing this for enjoyment. Probably only me and my other half will ever read this and comment. Maybe my mum too. I like to go running. I’m never going to be an Olympic athlete. So why do it? Sheer enjoyment. Although with running it doesn’t usually feel like it at the time! In an online world where everybody wants to be the best, earn the most. Get the most likes, page views, comments. Be noticed. I guess doing something for self-satisfaction feels a little strange. But maybe, that’s just me. Oh. So what have I learned? Well for one. I don’t need to quickly write a blog post, half-arse it, and say pretty much nothing interesting. Just to write ‘something’ Also rather than being a small fish in a very big pond. I’m more of a speck of dust floating in the universe. Don’t expect to be even noticed. You may get a few visitors, who then quickly click to something more interesting. Hell, I’ve done it myself. Clicked on something, read it, moved on. So I’m just as guilty. Write because you enjoy it. It’s therapeutic. Write for yourself. You’re not going to make $$$ a month. You’ll be frustrated trying and lose the enjoyment of blogging. This isn’t a pity post. More of, say, a reality check. A long rambling reality check that has a crappy ending.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cake Tuesday</title><link href="/cakes/2021/07/27/cake-tuesday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cake Tuesday" /><published>2021-07-27T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-27T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/cakes/2021/07/27/cake-tuesday</id><content type="html" xml:base="/cakes/2021/07/27/cake-tuesday/">&lt;p&gt;Many moons ago. In the dark and distant past. I had a blogger blog. An, if not successful, then maybe a slightly popular one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627389798/IMG_20210727_133019_428_uae4rr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then for some reason. I got bored with it.  And left it gathering dust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where for some reason blogging has sparked a small fire inside me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My girlfriend has stopped making celebration cakes. But the photos are still with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627389801/2_20210727_132650_0001_lsqmdl.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here I go. Resurrecting &lt;strong&gt;Cake&lt;/strong&gt; Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The original post can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2007/07/24/cake-tuesday/&quot; title=&quot;Safari Cake&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="cakes" /><summary type="html">Many moons ago. In the dark and distant past. I had a blogger blog. An, if not successful, then maybe a slightly popular one. And then for some reason. I got bored with it. And left it gathering dust. Until now. Where for some reason blogging has sparked a small fire inside me. My girlfriend has stopped making celebration cakes. But the photos are still with us. So here I go. Resurrecting Cake Tuesday. The original post can be found here.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">20 Things I’d Tell 20 Year Old Me</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/26/20-things-i-d-tell-20-year-old-me/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="20 Things I’d Tell 20 Year Old Me" /><published>2021-07-26T02:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-26T02:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/26/20-things-i-d-tell-20-year-old-me</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/26/20-things-i-d-tell-20-year-old-me/">&lt;p&gt;Turning 50, and then very quickly turning 51 has got me thinking of what I’d tell my younger self if I could go back in time. For the longest time, I’d say things like “no regrets” or “you only live once”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking back now I realise that was bullshit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a ton of regrets and wishing I’d looked before I leaped. And the further away from my youth I get the stronger these thoughts become.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627250358/canva_assets/20_Things_I_d_Tell_20_Year_Old_Me_agchzz.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take better care of yourself early on&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Look after your body. Sure, it can recover quicker from a night out at 20. But you’re going to feel it later in life. Brush your teeth twice a day. Properly. And have breakfast. Not a quick sip of coffee as you head out the door after being up and dressed in five minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are stronger than you know&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;You can and will survive so many things in later life. It might not feel like it at the time but you can get through anything. Especially if you follow the next point.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always take care of your mental health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;This is the single most important thing I can tell myself. Don’t be afraid to get the help you feel you need. Do not let others around you influence you. They are not you. They are not the ones going through what you are. Listen to their advice. But the end decision lies with you. DO NOT suffer in silence.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t believe everything everyone tells you&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Especially in the workplace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Everybody lies.  Even if they don’t realise they’re doing it. Or even mean to. Take everything you hear with a grain of salt. Stay out of workplace dramas. And stay away from workplace relationships. They never work out.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work to live don’t live to work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Not that I really need to tell myself this. Work isn’t everything. Don’t take the baggage of work home with you. And don’t stick with a job because you think you should.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t take things so personally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;You need a thicker skin. Do not take whatever anybody says to heart. People will lie, manipulate, dictate and criticise anything about you. They are not you. And their opinion of you is none of your business.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn to embrace change&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;There will be many changes in life, not all of them positive. Some changes you can change. Some you can’t. Don’t dwell on the things outside your control.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintain friendships&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Don’t shut people out. You will end up with nobody you can call a friend. They won’t and shouldn’t put up with your selfish crap. Your true friends will be there for you. But you need to be there for them to.  Don’t let life get in the way.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627250397/blog/undraw/undraw_Social_media_re_w12q_dbdqwh.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t worry about what others think or about what they are doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Don’t look at other people and compare what they have or want to you. You are not them and they are not you. They may drive a big, fast car and you trundle around in a 1L city car. They may earn more money, be healthier, fitter It doesn’t matter. Do not compare yourself to others.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s ok to get out of your comfort zone sometimes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Actually it’s probably healthy. Don’t stay in your own safe little bubble. You’ll become more confident and able to cope with the world around you if you live in it just a little sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are not your thoughts, you are the thinker of your thoughts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Your own mind can be your worst enemy at times. Seeds of doubt and self hate can grow and fester given enough time and energy. It’s a cliché to “think positive” but there’s also some truth in it. Try and not let the negative thoughts win so much.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always choose kindness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Another one I don’t really need to tell myself. But this includes everyone and everything in life. People as well as animals.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spend more time together&lt;/strong&gt; I cannot stress this enough. Make more time for family. Even if you have to do all the hard work.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627250397/blog/undraw/undraw_fatherhood_7i19_hysxfi.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;They’re not always going to be there. And when they’re gone you will have regrets about things left unsaid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everything happens for a reason&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Some of these things will be good. Some things will be bad. Some you can control and others you can’t.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on one thing at a time. You can have it all but not all at once&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Be patient. Be focused. Don’t let thoughts or frustrations cloud your mind. Do what makes you happy in the moment and don’t dwell on the other things you wish you could also do. You’ll half ass anything you try and do if your mind is elsewhere. You can’t juggle without dropping things.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s OK to be unsure about your purpose in life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;At 20, 30 or even 40. Life is ever changing.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t try too hard with people&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;You’ll push people away. You’ll lose good friends and ruin relationships before they have time to flourish. Saying less can be so much more effective than constantly speaking your mind.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;stand up and speak out for what’s important to you&lt;/strong&gt; Going slightly at odds with the list point. If you are passionate about an issue. You have a voice. Use it to help others. Don’t be preachy or ram it down people’s throats. Learn how to engage in debate to get your point across. It’s ok to disagree with someone. Don’t just go with the popular opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are not the only person in the world who feels this way&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;It often feels like it at times. But whatever you’re going through is not unique to you. Personal, yes. Share your thoughts and worries with like-minded people. Staying in your own head just makes the echo chamber resonate louder.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t stop learning&lt;/strong&gt; Ever. Don’t stop reading. Try new interests. Some will stick, some will drop off.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627250397/blog/undraw/undraw_exams_g4ow_jd1g7g.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;You will flourish at some and fail at others. Just enjoy the moment and don’t dwell on the ones that didn’t work out. It’s the journey that’s important. You’ll plateau, become frustrated and discard interests as you go through life. It’s ok. Just keep moving forward. Do what makes you happy whether it lasts 5 days or 5 years. Just enjoy the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="personal" /><summary type="html">Turning 50, and then very quickly turning 51 has got me thinking of what I’d tell my younger self if I could go back in time. For the longest time, I’d say things like “no regrets” or “you only live once” Looking back now I realise that was bullshit. I have a ton of regrets and wishing I’d looked before I leaped. And the further away from my youth I get the stronger these thoughts become. Take better care of yourself early on Look after your body. Sure, it can recover quicker from a night out at 20. But you’re going to feel it later in life. Brush your teeth twice a day. Properly. And have breakfast. Not a quick sip of coffee as you head out the door after being up and dressed in five minutes. You are stronger than you know You can and will survive so many things in later life. It might not feel like it at the time but you can get through anything. Especially if you follow the next point. Always take care of your mental health This is the single most important thing I can tell myself. Don’t be afraid to get the help you feel you need. Do not let others around you influence you. They are not you. They are not the ones going through what you are. Listen to their advice. But the end decision lies with you. DO NOT suffer in silence. Don’t believe everything everyone tells you. Especially in the workplace Everybody lies. Even if they don’t realise they’re doing it. Or even mean to. Take everything you hear with a grain of salt. Stay out of workplace dramas. And stay away from workplace relationships. They never work out. Work to live don’t live to work Not that I really need to tell myself this. Work isn’t everything. Don’t take the baggage of work home with you. And don’t stick with a job because you think you should. Don’t take things so personally You need a thicker skin. Do not take whatever anybody says to heart. People will lie, manipulate, dictate and criticise anything about you. They are not you. And their opinion of you is none of your business. Learn to embrace change There will be many changes in life, not all of them positive. Some changes you can change. Some you can’t. Don’t dwell on the things outside your control. Maintain friendships Don’t shut people out. You will end up with nobody you can call a friend. They won’t and shouldn’t put up with your selfish crap. Your true friends will be there for you. But you need to be there for them to. Don’t let life get in the way. Don’t worry about what others think or about what they are doing Don’t look at other people and compare what they have or want to you. You are not them and they are not you. They may drive a big, fast car and you trundle around in a 1L city car. They may earn more money, be healthier, fitter It doesn’t matter. Do not compare yourself to others. It’s ok to get out of your comfort zone sometimes Actually it’s probably healthy. Don’t stay in your own safe little bubble. You’ll become more confident and able to cope with the world around you if you live in it just a little sometimes. You are not your thoughts, you are the thinker of your thoughts Your own mind can be your worst enemy at times. Seeds of doubt and self hate can grow and fester given enough time and energy. It’s a cliché to “think positive” but there’s also some truth in it. Try and not let the negative thoughts win so much. Always choose kindness Another one I don’t really need to tell myself. But this includes everyone and everything in life. People as well as animals. Spend more time together I cannot stress this enough. Make more time for family. Even if you have to do all the hard work. They’re not always going to be there. And when they’re gone you will have regrets about things left unsaid. Everything happens for a reason Some of these things will be good. Some things will be bad. Some you can control and others you can’t. Focus on one thing at a time. You can have it all but not all at once Be patient. Be focused. Don’t let thoughts or frustrations cloud your mind. Do what makes you happy in the moment and don’t dwell on the other things you wish you could also do. You’ll half ass anything you try and do if your mind is elsewhere. You can’t juggle without dropping things. It’s OK to be unsure about your purpose in life At 20, 30 or even 40. Life is ever changing. Don’t try too hard with people You’ll push people away. You’ll lose good friends and ruin relationships before they have time to flourish. Saying less can be so much more effective than constantly speaking your mind. stand up and speak out for what’s important to you Going slightly at odds with the list point. If you are passionate about an issue. You have a voice. Use it to help others. Don’t be preachy or ram it down people’s throats. Learn how to engage in debate to get your point across. It’s ok to disagree with someone. Don’t just go with the popular opinion. You are not the only person in the world who feels this way It often feels like it at times. But whatever you’re going through is not unique to you. Personal, yes. Share your thoughts and worries with like-minded people. Staying in your own head just makes the echo chamber resonate louder. Don’t stop learning Ever. Don’t stop reading. Try new interests. Some will stick, some will drop off. You will flourish at some and fail at others. Just enjoy the moment and don’t dwell on the ones that didn’t work out. It’s the journey that’s important. You’ll plateau, become frustrated and discard interests as you go through life. It’s ok. Just keep moving forward. Do what makes you happy whether it lasts 5 days or 5 years. Just enjoy the moment.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Demotivation Monday</title><link href="/demotivation/2021/07/26/demotivation-monday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Demotivation Monday" /><published>2021-07-26T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-26T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/demotivation/2021/07/26/demotivation-monday</id><content type="html" xml:base="/demotivation/2021/07/26/demotivation-monday/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626977878/demotivation/stress.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="demotivation" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Are We Nearly There Yet?</title><link href="/c25k/depression/2021/07/24/are-we-nearly-there-yet/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Are We Nearly There Yet?" /><published>2021-07-24T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-24T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/c25k/depression/2021/07/24/are-we-nearly-there-yet</id><content type="html" xml:base="/c25k/depression/2021/07/24/are-we-nearly-there-yet/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627109545/c25k/c25kw3r3_ngnw6m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Week 3 is finally finished. I say week 3, but it must be more like 9 weeks as I’m only getting one run a week in. Which isn’t ideal. Motivation is just at rock bottom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a member of my local gym thanks to the discounted rate to join through my physio. I just have to get over my introverted nature and go more than once!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the problem. It’s a lack of self-belief that holds me back. There’s no way I should be at the gym. Everybody is younger, fitter with more muscles than i’ll ever have. So why bother?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s the thought constantly in my head. Why am I doing this? What do I hope to gain from the experience? You’ll only get frustrated at your inability to progress. You’ll hit a stumbling block and falter. And then get frustrated and quit. And move onto the next big, better thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And so it goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On and on. Round and round.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trying to cram a bit of me-time which doesn’t involve my partner, work or cats is difficult at the best of times. So I sit on the sofa and engross myself in a gadget, half watching the tv. Because it’s easy. And I can focus for the five minutes I might get before being interrupted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know this all sounds a bit “poor me”. And it is. If I really wanted something I’d put myself first wouldn’t I?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I don’t. Or at least, I don’t know how.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t think I can change. You can’t teach an old dog new tricks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So on I go, attempting to go into something 100% and only managing 20%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I’m just trying to fill the empty void. The hole in my heart where my dad and brother used to be. Finding a purpose in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you go. Week 3 is finished. I don’t feel a sense of accomplishment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Am I just wallowing in self-pity? Does anybody else feel this emptiness despite wanting to feel whole? And the frustration that I just doesn’t seem to want to happen?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just me? Ok.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="c25k" /><category term="depression" /><summary type="html">Week 3 is finally finished. I say week 3, but it must be more like 9 weeks as I’m only getting one run a week in. Which isn’t ideal. Motivation is just at rock bottom. I’m a member of my local gym thanks to the discounted rate to join through my physio. I just have to get over my introverted nature and go more than once! That’s the problem. It’s a lack of self-belief that holds me back. There’s no way I should be at the gym. Everybody is younger, fitter with more muscles than i’ll ever have. So why bother? And that’s the thought constantly in my head. Why am I doing this? What do I hope to gain from the experience? You’ll only get frustrated at your inability to progress. You’ll hit a stumbling block and falter. And then get frustrated and quit. And move onto the next big, better thing. And so it goes. On and on. Round and round. Trying to cram a bit of me-time which doesn’t involve my partner, work or cats is difficult at the best of times. So I sit on the sofa and engross myself in a gadget, half watching the tv. Because it’s easy. And I can focus for the five minutes I might get before being interrupted. I know this all sounds a bit “poor me”. And it is. If I really wanted something I’d put myself first wouldn’t I? But I don’t. Or at least, I don’t know how. I don’t think I can change. You can’t teach an old dog new tricks. So on I go, attempting to go into something 100% and only managing 20%. Maybe I’m just trying to fill the empty void. The hole in my heart where my dad and brother used to be. Finding a purpose in life. So there you go. Week 3 is finished. I don’t feel a sense of accomplishment. Am I just wallowing in self-pity? Does anybody else feel this emptiness despite wanting to feel whole? And the frustration that I just doesn’t seem to want to happen? Just me? Ok.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Pale Blue Dot</title><link href="/quotes/2021/07/22/pale-blue-dot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pale Blue Dot" /><published>2021-07-22T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-22T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/quotes/2021/07/22/pale-blue-dot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/quotes/2021/07/22/pale-blue-dot/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/c_scale,e_vignette:20,h_400/v1626973888/blog/earth.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;hand holding a globe&quot; title=&quot;Earth in the Palm of your Hand&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Look again at that dot. That’s here. That’s home. That’s us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every “superstar,” every “supreme leader,” every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena. Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds. Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet. Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we’ve ever known.”&lt;br /&gt;
― &lt;strong&gt;Carl Sagan,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/work/quotes/1816628&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pale Blue Dot: A Vision of the Human Future in Space&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo by&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pexels.com/@nurseryart?utm_content=attributionCopyText&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=pexels&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Porapak Apichodilok&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;from&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pexels.com/photo/person-holding-world-globe-facing-mountain-346885/?utm_content=attributionCopyText&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=pexels&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pexels&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="quotes" /><summary type="html">“Look again at that dot. That’s here. That’s home. That’s us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every “superstar,” every “supreme leader,” every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam. The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena. Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds. Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot. Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves. The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet. Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand. It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we’ve ever known.” ― Carl Sagan, Pale Blue Dot: A Vision of the Human Future in Space Photo by Porapak Apichodilok from Pexels</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sharing a Post</title><link href="/depression/2021/07/19/sharing-a-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sharing a Post" /><published>2021-07-19T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-19T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/depression/2021/07/19/sharing-a-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="/depression/2021/07/19/sharing-a-post/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626687653/blog/depression_by_destinyblue_d8u7vu2_ufgodr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Hi I’m Blue, and I struggle with mental illness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Some of you will dismiss me, some of you will be scared of me, some of you will blame me, but a surprising amount of you will understand me, because 1 in 4 people experience mental health issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.deviantart.com/destinyblue/art/Depression-534485738&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; on deviantart.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="depression" /><summary type="html">Hi I’m Blue, and I struggle with mental illness. Some of you will dismiss me, some of you will be scared of me, some of you will blame me, but a surprising amount of you will understand me, because 1 in 4 people experience mental health issues. Read more here on deviantart.com</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Quote of the Day</title><link href="/quotes/depression/2021/07/18/quote-of-the-day/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quote of the Day" /><published>2021-07-18T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-18T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/quotes/depression/2021/07/18/quote-of-the-day</id><content type="html" xml:base="/quotes/depression/2021/07/18/quote-of-the-day/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626598335/quotes/No_one_is_ever_happy_until_you_ve_taken_on_the_same_level_of_responsibility_they_are_unhappy_with_in_their_own_lives._wgbwmr.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The older I get, the more this sentence resonates with me. I don’t know if I’m just getting more cynical, jaded. If I’m just surrounded by such people that their negativity is rubbing off on me. If it’s world politics, events, or the pandemic. I just know there’s an overwhelming aura of despair that blankets my entire view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are moments of happiness that poke through the holes in this blanket. Little points of light shining through. But these don’t last long. Like coming up for air, flailing in the deep waters. These brief moments of sweet, fresh air are soon lost in the dark, unforgiving water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that’s enough terrible analogies that only a 15-year-old emo kid would be happy with. I’m 51, and the older I get the more these jaded thoughts are strengthened. Maybe I need to surround myself with more positive people. They must exist out there somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="quotes" /><category term="depression" /><summary type="html">The older I get, the more this sentence resonates with me. I don’t know if I’m just getting more cynical, jaded. If I’m just surrounded by such people that their negativity is rubbing off on me. If it’s world politics, events, or the pandemic. I just know there’s an overwhelming aura of despair that blankets my entire view. There are moments of happiness that poke through the holes in this blanket. Little points of light shining through. But these don’t last long. Like coming up for air, flailing in the deep waters. These brief moments of sweet, fresh air are soon lost in the dark, unforgiving water. I think that’s enough terrible analogies that only a 15-year-old emo kid would be happy with. I’m 51, and the older I get the more these jaded thoughts are strengthened. Maybe I need to surround myself with more positive people. They must exist out there somewhere.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>