<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-GB"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-GB" /><updated>2021-08-20T22:11:52+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blog.thisispaddys.space</title><subtitle>Home</subtitle><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><entry><title type="html">Keeping Life In Focus - Without Losing Interest</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/mental-health/2021/08/20/keeping-life-in-focus/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Keeping Life In Focus - Without Losing Interest" /><published>2021-08-20T02:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-20T02:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/mental-health/2021/08/20/keeping-life-in-focus</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/mental-health/2021/08/20/keeping-life-in-focus/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keeping Focus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I can feel it happening. It’s not like the bubble bursting. More like, it’s slowly deflating.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve gone from going flat out, foot to the floor. Pedal to the metal. Well, you get the idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest shiny new thing in my life is starting to dull.  I don’t know how it starts. What triggers it off. But the slow decline of an interest begins a new upward trajectory in my depression. And it’s really annoying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why does it happen? What causes me to lose interest in something, anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--read more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s no time scale. It can be days, weeks or months later. When I feel I’m getting into my stride. The slow hiss of escaping air from the bubble begins. Until it’s deafening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not going to have any answers unfortunately. There are better bloggers, better Google searches you could do to find more accurate, relevant and interesting information than you’ll find here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe this post is just a rant about my current state of mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why do I lose interest?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The quick answer would be depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But why do I get excited about something to begin with then?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anhedonia&quot;&gt;Anhedonia&lt;/a&gt; comes up in Google searches. But doesn’t really resonate with me. Because I still gets bursts of excitement and interest in things. No matter how short lived.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Low confidence. That paired with depression and a sense of belonging. The early stages of excitement in a new hobby, project or whatever it may be overrides the negative thoughts that whisper to me. I have found my sense of purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any new interest is always exciting. You are on the new adventure of learning. You know nothing about this thing. Your brain is ready to be filled with new teachings. And then it starts to happen. The second I plateau the rot sets in. The frustration at my inability to progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why did I start this in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was I thinking?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I actually think I could become good at this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t remember anything of what I’ve learned?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is hopeless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re hopeless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know how I could have found this interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then like somebody waving a magic wand the passion is gone. And I’m left looking at this interest like it’s a strange, incomprehensible thing. Why would I be interested in that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except I have this faint memory of finding it interesting at some point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that leaves me feeling sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can I reignite the spark?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related Article: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;amp;source=web&amp;amp;rct=j&amp;amp;url=https://www.verywellmind.com/things-to-do-if-you-feel-a-loss-of-interest-5093337&amp;amp;ved=2ahUKEwjMpc2X2b_yAhXxRUEAHVsYCF0QFnoECAMQAQ&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw3PF0UuDXSbe2yV_R51Z7p4&quot;&gt;5 Things To Do If We Feel A Loss Of Interest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one slight silver lining in this very dark cloud is. Yes. Well, sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve lost interest in learning a new language due to frustration, only to try again months later. Oh I still got frustrated and dropped it again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, bad example. Web development. Got a few books, learned a bit of html, CSS and suchlike only to again drop it due to frustrations in my limited abilities.  But. I started again along with my new found love for blogging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blogging and web development seem to go well together. They feed off each other. And I’m finding that I’m still learning. Well. I was. Despite the initial excitement, I can feel the bubble starting to wobble.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m hoping it’s a natural wobble that, probably, every blogger goes through. Especially in the early days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to just go with the flow. A saying I’ve used throughout my life, but one I struggle with listening to the older I get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So what now?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not every wobble ends in disaster. It’s just a speed bump. I need to slow down. And just focus on the road ahead. Easier said than done. But one I need to learn from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, why bother starting anything new in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="mental-health" /><summary type="html">Keeping Focus I can feel it happening. It’s not like the bubble bursting. More like, it’s slowly deflating. I’ve gone from going flat out, foot to the floor. Pedal to the metal. Well, you get the idea. The latest shiny new thing in my life is starting to dull. I don’t know how it starts. What triggers it off. But the slow decline of an interest begins a new upward trajectory in my depression. And it’s really annoying. So why does it happen? What causes me to lose interest in something, anything. There’s no time scale. It can be days, weeks or months later. When I feel I’m getting into my stride. The slow hiss of escaping air from the bubble begins. Until it’s deafening. I’m not going to have any answers unfortunately. There are better bloggers, better Google searches you could do to find more accurate, relevant and interesting information than you’ll find here. Maybe this post is just a rant about my current state of mind. Why do I lose interest? The quick answer would be depression. But why do I get excited about something to begin with then? Anhedonia comes up in Google searches. But doesn’t really resonate with me. Because I still gets bursts of excitement and interest in things. No matter how short lived. Low confidence. That paired with depression and a sense of belonging. The early stages of excitement in a new hobby, project or whatever it may be overrides the negative thoughts that whisper to me. I have found my sense of purpose. Any new interest is always exciting. You are on the new adventure of learning. You know nothing about this thing. Your brain is ready to be filled with new teachings. And then it starts to happen. The second I plateau the rot sets in. The frustration at my inability to progress. Why did I start this in the first place? What was I thinking? Did I actually think I could become good at this? I can’t remember anything of what I’ve learned? This is hopeless. You’re hopeless. I don’t know how I could have found this interesting. And then like somebody waving a magic wand the passion is gone. And I’m left looking at this interest like it’s a strange, incomprehensible thing. Why would I be interested in that? Except I have this faint memory of finding it interesting at some point. And that leaves me feeling sad. Can I reignite the spark? Related Article: 5 Things To Do If We Feel A Loss Of Interest The one slight silver lining in this very dark cloud is. Yes. Well, sometimes. I’ve lost interest in learning a new language due to frustration, only to try again months later. Oh I still got frustrated and dropped it again. Ok, bad example. Web development. Got a few books, learned a bit of html, CSS and suchlike only to again drop it due to frustrations in my limited abilities. But. I started again along with my new found love for blogging. Blogging and web development seem to go well together. They feed off each other. And I’m finding that I’m still learning. Well. I was. Despite the initial excitement, I can feel the bubble starting to wobble. I’m hoping it’s a natural wobble that, probably, every blogger goes through. Especially in the early days. I need to just go with the flow. A saying I’ve used throughout my life, but one I struggle with listening to the older I get. So what now? Not every wobble ends in disaster. It’s just a speed bump. I need to slow down. And just focus on the road ahead. Easier said than done. But one I need to learn from. Otherwise, why bother starting anything new in the first place.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">When You’re An Introvert At The Gym - Infographic</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/mental-healrh/2021/08/20/when-you-re-an-introvert-at-the-gym-infographic/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When You’re An Introvert At The Gym - Infographic" /><published>2021-08-20T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-20T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/mental-healrh/2021/08/20/when-you-re-an-introvert-at-the-gym-infographic</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/mental-healrh/2021/08/20/when-you-re-an-introvert-at-the-gym-infographic/">&lt;p&gt;A tl;dr of my &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/2021/08/18/and-when-you-re-up/&quot; title=&quot;When You're An Introvert At The Gym&quot;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1629433824/infographic/beinganintrovert_jmdgfn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Printable pdf can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.thisispaddys.space/pdf.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="running" /><category term="mental-healrh" /><summary type="html">A tl;dr of my previous post. Printable pdf can be found here</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">When You’re An Introvert At The Gym</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/2021/08/18/and-when-you-re-up/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When You’re An Introvert At The Gym" /><published>2021-08-18T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-18T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/2021/08/18/and-when-you-re-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/2021/08/18/and-when-you-re-up/">&lt;p&gt;What a difference 48 hours can make..After my previous visit to the gym went &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/2021/08/12/a-running-low/&quot; title=&quot;Running low&quot;&gt;horribly badly&lt;/a&gt;, friday did a complete 180 and restored faith in myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“No one can make you feel inferior without your consent.” – Eleanor Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wasn’t going to let the gym win. It wasn’t going to take the enjoyment out of my training. Mentally I went in ready to face my fears. And, I won. It, admittedly, did help by the fact the gym was fairly empty. The people in there were the same age, or older than me. I felt relaxed. All the tension that I had melted away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remember:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nobody is judging you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t compare yourself to others&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep your workouts short&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do what you love&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wear headphones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go In Off Peak Hours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;game-plan&quot;&gt;Game Plan&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was ready. I had a game plan. If the upstairs area with all the cross trainers, exercise bikes and treadmills was busy, i’d go downstairs and use the leg press and other torture devices. And visa versa. if both areas were busy i’d just go home and try again the next day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;nobody-is-judging-you&quot;&gt;Nobody is Judging you&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite thinking you’re going to be the center of attention, everybody is in their own little bubble trying to ignore everybody else. Chances are some are even as introverted as you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Your of the gym and certainty that I was being judged came from my thoughts and beliefs—not theirs.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;related-article&quot;&gt;Related Article&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://routineexcellence.com/stop-feeling-judged-gym-psychology-gym-anxiety/&quot; title=&quot;How to Stop Feeling Judged at the Gym: The Psychology of Gym Anxiety&quot;&gt;How to Stop Feeling Judged at the Gym: The Psychology of Gym Anxiety&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;dont-compare-yourself-to-others&quot;&gt;Don’t Compare Yourself To Others&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a difficult, but important one. They aren’t you, and you aren’t them. You have to travel your own path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;related-article-1&quot;&gt;Related Article&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.self.com/story/comparing-yourself-to-others-wont-help-you-meet-your-goals&quot; title=&quot;Comparing Yourself to Others Won't Help You Meet Your Goals&quot;&gt;Comparing Yourself to Others Won’t Help You Meet Your Goals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;keep-your-workouts-short&quot;&gt;Keep your workouts short&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You don’t need to spend all day in the gym. You don’t need to be there for hours. An hour even. Small bursts of exercise throughout the day are just as effective as one longer session. Just 30 minutes of exercise is more than enough time to get in a great workout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;related-article-2&quot;&gt;Related Article&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/guides/well/strength-training-plyometrics&quot; title=&quot;The 9-Minute Strength Workout&quot;&gt;The 9-Minute Strength Workout&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;wear-headphones-earbuds&quot;&gt;Wear &lt;del&gt;headphones&lt;/del&gt; earbuds&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a no-brainer. The music at the gym is terrible. You can be in your own little bubble. People will usually not try and talk to you. It’s easier to just blank out the entire world around you. Also you’re not left with your own thoughts bouncing around in your head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bluetooth earbuds are ideal for wearing to the gym. Don’t use headphones, they tend to be bulky in size and don’t stay put.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;related-article-3&quot;&gt;Related Article&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.taotronics.com/headphones/5-reasons-take-wireless-earbuds-to-gym/&quot; title=&quot;5 Reasons You Should Take Wireless Earbuds to the Gym&quot;&gt;5 Reasons You Should Take Wireless Earbuds to the Gym&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;go-in-off-peak-hours&quot;&gt;Go In Off Peak Hours&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This might vary from gym to gym. But generally speaking:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weekdays around lunch or in the early afternoon.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Late at night (past 8 pm if your gym is still open)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weekends in the mid to late afternoon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I usually go after work at about 5pm and it can be very hit and miss as to how busy the gym is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;related-article-4&quot;&gt;Related Article&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fitnessfirst.co.uk/inside-track/fitness/when-is-the-best-time-to-exercise/&quot; title=&quot;When Is The Best Time To Exercise?&quot;&gt;When Is The Best Time To Exercise?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stick at it and the gym is something you get used to. Countless others have been in your shoes, myself included. Think nothing of any judgment you think may be occurring because everyone else will almost certainly be doing their own thing. Easier said than done, but it will happen at some point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be kind to yourself. If it’s too busy go again another day. Just do a short workout. The more you go the more the gym will become a familiar place. You’ll start seeing the same faces regularly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And chances are some of those familiar faces will be feeling exactly the same as you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;links&quot;&gt;Links&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://introvertdear.com/news/how-to-survive-going-to-the-gym-when-youre-an-introvert/&quot; title=&quot;How to Survive Going to the Gym When You’re an Introvert&quot;&gt;How to Survive Going to the Gym When You’re an Introvert&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/an-introverts-guide-to-enjoying-exercise-by-introverts_uk_5e299860c5b6779e9c2e8159&quot; title=&quot;An Introvert's Guide To Enjoying Exercise – By Introverts&quot;&gt;An Introvert’s Guide To Enjoying Exercise – By Introverts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.self.com/story/gym-tips-to-gain-confidence&quot; title=&quot;12 Ways to Go From Newbie to Gym Regular&quot;&gt;12 Ways to Go From Newbie to Gym Regular&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://femalefitnesssystems.com/improve-confidence-in-the-gym/&quot; title=&quot;7 Simple And Effective Tips To Boost Confidence In The Gym&quot;&gt;7 Simple And Effective Tips To Boost Confidence In The Gym&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="running" /><summary type="html">What a difference 48 hours can make..After my previous visit to the gym went horribly badly, friday did a complete 180 and restored faith in myself. “No one can make you feel inferior without your consent.” – Eleanor Roosevelt I wasn’t going to let the gym win. It wasn’t going to take the enjoyment out of my training. Mentally I went in ready to face my fears. And, I won. It, admittedly, did help by the fact the gym was fairly empty. The people in there were the same age, or older than me. I felt relaxed. All the tension that I had melted away. Remember: Nobody is judging you Don’t compare yourself to others Keep your workouts short Do what you love Wear headphones Go In Off Peak Hours Game Plan I was ready. I had a game plan. If the upstairs area with all the cross trainers, exercise bikes and treadmills was busy, i’d go downstairs and use the leg press and other torture devices. And visa versa. if both areas were busy i’d just go home and try again the next day. Nobody is Judging you Despite thinking you’re going to be the center of attention, everybody is in their own little bubble trying to ignore everybody else. Chances are some are even as introverted as you. Your of the gym and certainty that I was being judged came from my thoughts and beliefs—not theirs. Related Article How to Stop Feeling Judged at the Gym: The Psychology of Gym Anxiety Don’t Compare Yourself To Others This is a difficult, but important one. They aren’t you, and you aren’t them. You have to travel your own path. Related Article Comparing Yourself to Others Won’t Help You Meet Your Goals Keep your workouts short You don’t need to spend all day in the gym. You don’t need to be there for hours. An hour even. Small bursts of exercise throughout the day are just as effective as one longer session. Just 30 minutes of exercise is more than enough time to get in a great workout. Related Article The 9-Minute Strength Workout Wear headphones earbuds This is a no-brainer. The music at the gym is terrible. You can be in your own little bubble. People will usually not try and talk to you. It’s easier to just blank out the entire world around you. Also you’re not left with your own thoughts bouncing around in your head. Bluetooth earbuds are ideal for wearing to the gym. Don’t use headphones, they tend to be bulky in size and don’t stay put. Related Article 5 Reasons You Should Take Wireless Earbuds to the Gym Go In Off Peak Hours This might vary from gym to gym. But generally speaking: Weekdays around lunch or in the early afternoon. Late at night (past 8 pm if your gym is still open) Weekends in the mid to late afternoon. I usually go after work at about 5pm and it can be very hit and miss as to how busy the gym is. Related Article When Is The Best Time To Exercise? Stick at it and the gym is something you get used to. Countless others have been in your shoes, myself included. Think nothing of any judgment you think may be occurring because everyone else will almost certainly be doing their own thing. Easier said than done, but it will happen at some point. Be kind to yourself. If it’s too busy go again another day. Just do a short workout. The more you go the more the gym will become a familiar place. You’ll start seeing the same faces regularly. And chances are some of those familiar faces will be feeling exactly the same as you. Links How to Survive Going to the Gym When You’re an Introvert An Introvert’s Guide To Enjoying Exercise – By Introverts 12 Ways to Go From Newbie to Gym Regular 7 Simple And Effective Tips To Boost Confidence In The Gym</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cake Tuesday</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2021/08/17/cake-tuesday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cake Tuesday" /><published>2021-08-17T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-17T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2021/08/17/cake-tuesday</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2021/08/17/cake-tuesday/">&lt;p&gt;My late father always loved the cakes Zara made. The ideas she came up with. The little things she got in the designs. The accuracy of the details. I think this was one of his favourites. Anything that involved his beloved rats always went down well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1629101063/cake-tuesday/2005_0622Image0004_2_.0_az3tdi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;He always sat in his favourite chair. With a cup of tea. And a slice of toast. And was always joined by his furry companions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1629101063/cake-tuesday/2005_0622Image0009.0_h6gckb.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The original post can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2006/05/09/cake-tuesday_09/&quot; title=&quot;Cake Tueday&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="cakes" /><summary type="html">My late father always loved the cakes Zara made. The ideas she came up with. The little things she got in the designs. The accuracy of the details. I think this was one of his favourites. Anything that involved his beloved rats always went down well. He always sat in his favourite chair. With a cup of tea. And a slice of toast. And was always joined by his furry companions. The original post can be found here</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Running…</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/2021/08/12/a-running-low/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Running…" /><published>2021-08-12T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-12T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/2021/08/12/a-running-low</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/2021/08/12/a-running-low/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;feeling-the-runners-high-low&quot;&gt;Feeling the runner’s &lt;del&gt;high&lt;/del&gt; low&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1628777017/c25k/fitbitshare_982746285_2_t9ypfr.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I should be happy. But I felt like a fraud. I felt out of place at the gym. I felt like I didn’t belong. It’s nobody’s fault except my own. Nobody shamed me. Looked down on me. Ridiculed me. I did that to myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw myself in the mirror whilst on the leg press.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This, skinny old man stared back at me. With legs that looked like they could snap and a tired old face. No muscles to be seen. How could I ever think I’d belong in a place like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t run because of leg pain. I just felt useless. I’m doubting my ability to run. I’m twice the age of everybody around me. And feeling every one of those years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d sat on the leg press. Whoever used it before me was pressing 100kg. I reduced that down to a pitiful 25kg. I shouldn’t do that. I shouldn’t compare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;Comparison is the thief of joy&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it’s not that easy when you’re surrounded by thieves. And I let them take everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The depression and self loathing can be crippling. Once it sets in there’s no going back. I had to get out of the gym quickly after that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe tomorrow will be better. Maybe if I wasn’t in there on my own I wouldn’t feel so vulnerable. But the dark side of me pushes people away. Or just won’t let them get close.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess I have to expect the lows with the highs. I’m still nervous after recovering from my knee injury. Probably too nervous. My left calf is now painful when I run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not going to give up after falling at the first hurdle. But it came as a shock. Maybe every runner goes through this. Maybe this isn’t as unusual as I think it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder if professional athletes have these moments. These thoughts. These feelings of runners low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe tomorrow will be better.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="running" /><summary type="html">Feeling the runner’s high low I should be happy. But I felt like a fraud. I felt out of place at the gym. I felt like I didn’t belong. It’s nobody’s fault except my own. Nobody shamed me. Looked down on me. Ridiculed me. I did that to myself. I saw myself in the mirror whilst on the leg press. This, skinny old man stared back at me. With legs that looked like they could snap and a tired old face. No muscles to be seen. How could I ever think I’d belong in a place like this. I couldn’t run because of leg pain. I just felt useless. I’m doubting my ability to run. I’m twice the age of everybody around me. And feeling every one of those years. I’d sat on the leg press. Whoever used it before me was pressing 100kg. I reduced that down to a pitiful 25kg. I shouldn’t do that. I shouldn’t compare. “Comparison is the thief of joy” But it’s not that easy when you’re surrounded by thieves. And I let them take everything. The depression and self loathing can be crippling. Once it sets in there’s no going back. I had to get out of the gym quickly after that. Maybe tomorrow will be better. Maybe if I wasn’t in there on my own I wouldn’t feel so vulnerable. But the dark side of me pushes people away. Or just won’t let them get close. I guess I have to expect the lows with the highs. I’m still nervous after recovering from my knee injury. Probably too nervous. My left calf is now painful when I run. I’m not going to give up after falling at the first hurdle. But it came as a shock. Maybe every runner goes through this. Maybe this isn’t as unusual as I think it is. I wonder if professional athletes have these moments. These thoughts. These feelings of runners low. Maybe tomorrow will be better.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Cake Tuesday</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/cake-tuesday/2021/08/10/cake-tuesday-1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cake Tuesday" /><published>2021-08-10T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-10T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/cake-tuesday/2021/08/10/cake-tuesday-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/cake-tuesday/2021/08/10/cake-tuesday-1/">&lt;p&gt;Going back further in time for this one. The first-ever Cake Tuesday. Not the first celebration cake. But the first one I decided to share with the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1628576842/cake-tuesday/Bath_cake_zur1fi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s my birthday cake from FIFTEEN YEARS AGO!! That can’t be right. When I was THIRTY SIX. Oh god I feel so old!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.thisispaddys.space/2006/05/02/cake-tuesday/&quot; title=&quot;Cake Tuesday&quot;&gt;here’s&lt;/a&gt; the original post from 2006. I think I need to go for a lay down now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="cakes" /><category term="cake-tuesday" /><summary type="html">Going back further in time for this one. The first-ever Cake Tuesday. Not the first celebration cake. But the first one I decided to share with the world. It’s my birthday cake from FIFTEEN YEARS AGO!! That can’t be right. When I was THIRTY SIX. Oh god I feel so old! Anyway, here’s the original post from 2006. I think I need to go for a lay down now.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">8 Things I wish I knew before I started running</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/c25k/2021/08/06/things-i-wish-i-knew-before-i-started-running/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="8 Things I wish I knew before I started running" /><published>2021-08-06T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-06T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/c25k/2021/08/06/things-i-wish-i-knew-before-i-started-running</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/running/c25k/2021/08/06/things-i-wish-i-knew-before-i-started-running/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1628363292/c25k/8_Things_I_wish_I_knew_before_I_started_running_insta.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still consider myself new to running. I started about a year ago. Then injured my knee and been slowly getting back into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with all things I threw myself into it 110%. Running every other day, Not exercising&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;8-the-things-i-wish-i-knew&quot;&gt;8 The Things I Wish I Knew&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Slow and Steady&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There’s Nothing Wrong With Walking&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rest Days Matter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strength Training&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Listen To Your Body&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Never Compare&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drink Plenty of Water&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wear The Right Shoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;things-i-wish-i-knew-before-i-started-running&quot;&gt;Things I wish I knew before I started running&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Slow And Steady&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst thing I did was go off like a greyhound, and keep going until it felt like my lungs would explode. Following the couch to 5k app with a mixture of running/walking helped slow down my pace. Which brings me onto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There’s Nothing Wrong With Walking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless you’re trying to break a world record or get a PB then slowing down for a walk is ok. It’s preferable to pushng too far and risking injury. It doesn’t make you any less of a runner. It’s not cheating. And there’s nothing wrong with using walking and running to improve your fitness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rest Days Matter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This toook me a while to realise. In my excitement to begin my runninh journey I did way too much in the beginning. Running every moment I could, playing Ring Fit on the Nintendo Switch when I couldn’t. I was putting my body through too much too soon. Which might be ok when you’re younger. But at 50….not so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strength Training&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought all I needed to do was run. Increase my stamina. Run. Increase my strength. Run. Well turns out that wasn’t the best for my muscles. Lifting weights, using resistence bands. Even yoga that helps muscle groups is all important things to consider on your running journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listen To Your Body&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The single worst thing I did was ignore my aches and pains. I thought I was just old and out of shape. The more I run the looser my muscles will become. Wrong. No pain no gain. Doubly wrong. I was soon off work with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.webmd.com/pain-management/knee-pain/meniscus-tear-injury&quot; title=&quot;torn meniscus&quot;&gt;torn meniscus&lt;/a&gt;. Weeks of rest and weeks of physio and I’m finally back running. But i’m wary of pushing myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never Compare&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The one contributing factor to my injury was getting a fitbit, uploading my times to fitbit and strava and seeing how my times stacked up to others. When I saw my pace was slower than a turtle in peanut butter then I pushed myself. Too hard. So remember:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Comparison Is The Thief Of Joy”&lt;/em&gt; - Theodore Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drink Plenty of Water&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dehydration negatively affects your running performance and slows your ability to recover. It increases muscle fatigue and exhaustion. Drinking before a run is so so important. Drink when you’re thirsty. Seems like an obvious thing to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Feeling thirsty happens after you are dehydrated,” explains Dr. Martha Pyron, MD of &lt;a href=&quot;https://medinmotion.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medicine in Motion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. “You should try to prevent feeling thirsty.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wear The Right Shoes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do your feet ache after a run, feeling numbness?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You can’t get your shoes off without completely loosening the laces&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After a long run, your arches ache, your Achilles-tendon is tender, and/or you feel strain in your calves&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Numbness or strain on the top of your foot&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your toes burn after a run&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chances are you aren’t wearing suitable shoes. Those ratty old trainers aren’t doing your feet any favours. I ended up going to a dedicates running shop. They analysed my running style and picked out a pair of running shoes. And they’ve been my best investment yet in my running journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-what-did-i-learn&quot;&gt;So What did I learn?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Don’t try to do too much too soon. Listen to your what your body is telling you. Don’t try to run through the pain. The risk of injury is very real. Try and get proper running shoes as soon as possible. And run for yourself. You can’t run too slow. But you can run too fast and risk injury. And stay hydrated!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And try to run for fun. Your body will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="running" /><category term="c25k" /><summary type="html">I still consider myself new to running. I started about a year ago. Then injured my knee and been slowly getting back into it. As with all things I threw myself into it 110%. Running every other day, Not exercising 8 The Things I Wish I Knew Slow and Steady There’s Nothing Wrong With Walking Rest Days Matter Strength Training Listen To Your Body Never Compare Drink Plenty of Water Wear The Right Shoes Things I wish I knew before I started running Slow And Steady The worst thing I did was go off like a greyhound, and keep going until it felt like my lungs would explode. Following the couch to 5k app with a mixture of running/walking helped slow down my pace. Which brings me onto There’s Nothing Wrong With Walking Unless you’re trying to break a world record or get a PB then slowing down for a walk is ok. It’s preferable to pushng too far and risking injury. It doesn’t make you any less of a runner. It’s not cheating. And there’s nothing wrong with using walking and running to improve your fitness. Rest Days Matter This toook me a while to realise. In my excitement to begin my runninh journey I did way too much in the beginning. Running every moment I could, playing Ring Fit on the Nintendo Switch when I couldn’t. I was putting my body through too much too soon. Which might be ok when you’re younger. But at 50….not so much. Strength Training I thought all I needed to do was run. Increase my stamina. Run. Increase my strength. Run. Well turns out that wasn’t the best for my muscles. Lifting weights, using resistence bands. Even yoga that helps muscle groups is all important things to consider on your running journey. Listen To Your Body The single worst thing I did was ignore my aches and pains. I thought I was just old and out of shape. The more I run the looser my muscles will become. Wrong. No pain no gain. Doubly wrong. I was soon off work with a torn meniscus. Weeks of rest and weeks of physio and I’m finally back running. But i’m wary of pushing myself. Never Compare The one contributing factor to my injury was getting a fitbit, uploading my times to fitbit and strava and seeing how my times stacked up to others. When I saw my pace was slower than a turtle in peanut butter then I pushed myself. Too hard. So remember: “Comparison Is The Thief Of Joy” - Theodore Roosevelt Drink Plenty of Water Dehydration negatively affects your running performance and slows your ability to recover. It increases muscle fatigue and exhaustion. Drinking before a run is so so important. Drink when you’re thirsty. Seems like an obvious thing to say. “Feeling thirsty happens after you are dehydrated,” explains Dr. Martha Pyron, MD of Medicine in Motion. “You should try to prevent feeling thirsty.” Wear The Right Shoes Do your feet ache after a run, feeling numbness? You can’t get your shoes off without completely loosening the laces After a long run, your arches ache, your Achilles-tendon is tender, and/or you feel strain in your calves Numbness or strain on the top of your foot Your toes burn after a run Chances are you aren’t wearing suitable shoes. Those ratty old trainers aren’t doing your feet any favours. I ended up going to a dedicates running shop. They analysed my running style and picked out a pair of running shoes. And they’ve been my best investment yet in my running journey. So What did I learn? Don’t try to do too much too soon. Listen to your what your body is telling you. Don’t try to run through the pain. The risk of injury is very real. Try and get proper running shoes as soon as possible. And run for yourself. You can’t run too slow. But you can run too fast and risk injury. And stay hydrated! And try to run for fun. Your body will thank you.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Discworld Cake Tuesday</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2021/08/03/discworld-cake-tuesday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Discworld Cake Tuesday" /><published>2021-08-03T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-08-03T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2021/08/03/discworld-cake-tuesday</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2021/08/03/discworld-cake-tuesday/">&lt;p&gt;Since the age of 16 when a college friend thrust a well read book into my hand and told me to read it saying&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’ve got to read this. Death is in it, and he turns up with cocktail sticks”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been hooked on the late great &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.terrypratchettbooks.com/&quot; title=&quot;Terry Pratchett&quot;&gt;Terry Pratchett&lt;/a&gt;’s Discworld. The obsession has wained slightly over the years. I’ve read the books, listened to the audiobooks, and watched the TV adaptations*( the only exception being the watch which is an abomination unto Nuggen) that it’s just a part of my DNA. I don’t feel the need to consume the media as obsessively as I did. But every time I think about the Discworld it makes me smile with wonderful memories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like this one! What a fantastic segway into this cake Tuesday offering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627983722/2004_0319Image0062_1_h6adnq.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mother who is equally as enthralled in the Discworld received this lovely creation for her birthday many years ago. I still think it’s her favourite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627983722/2004_0324Image0066_yc04bf.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture quality may not be the best. I might try and dig out some better photos if they exist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are other Discworld cakes that will appear along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The original post for this cake can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.archives.thisispaddys.space/cakes/2006/07/25/cake-tuesday_25/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="cakes" /><summary type="html">Since the age of 16 when a college friend thrust a well read book into my hand and told me to read it saying “You’ve got to read this. Death is in it, and he turns up with cocktail sticks” I’ve been hooked on the late great Terry Pratchett’s Discworld. The obsession has wained slightly over the years. I’ve read the books, listened to the audiobooks, and watched the TV adaptations*( the only exception being the watch which is an abomination unto Nuggen) that it’s just a part of my DNA. I don’t feel the need to consume the media as obsessively as I did. But every time I think about the Discworld it makes me smile with wonderful memories. Like this one! What a fantastic segway into this cake Tuesday offering. My mother who is equally as enthralled in the Discworld received this lovely creation for her birthday many years ago. I still think it’s her favourite. The picture quality may not be the best. I might try and dig out some better photos if they exist. There are other Discworld cakes that will appear along the way. The original post for this cake can be found here.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Top Terry Pratchett Caturday Quotes</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/caturday/2021/07/31/top-terry-pratchett-caturday-quotes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Top Terry Pratchett Caturday Quotes" /><published>2021-07-31T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-31T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/caturday/2021/07/31/top-terry-pratchett-caturday-quotes</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/caturday/2021/07/31/top-terry-pratchett-caturday-quotes/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;favourite-quotes&quot;&gt;Favourite quotes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just a few of my favourite cat-related quotes from my favourite author. The late, great &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.terrypratchettbooks.com/&quot; title=&quot;Sir Terry Pratchett&quot;&gt;Sir Terry Pratchett&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627672791/quotes/pratchett-cat-quote-0_ofvinm.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;The cat wonderfully posing in the pictures is Sam.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627672796/quotes/pratchett-cat-quote-1_llilsm.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;Sam actually lived 10 houses down from us. But decided to move in with his brother.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627672802/quotes/pratchett-cat-quote-2_tfpz7m.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;We eventually found out where he lived.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627672808/quotes/pratchett-cat-quote-3_hpsxrj.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;He moved back home, whilst his brother stayed with us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;honorable-mentions&quot;&gt;Honorable Mentions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Assassin moved quietly from roof to roof until he was well away from the excitement around the Watch House. His movements could be called cat-like, except that he did not stop to spray urine up against things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s an interesting fact that fewer than 17 % of Real cats end their lives with the same name they started with. Much family effort goes into selecting one at the start (“She looks like a Winnifred to me”), and then as the years roll by it suddenly finds itself being called Meepo or Ratbag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate cats.” Death’s face became a little stiffer, if that were possible. The blue glow in his eye sockets flickered red for an instant. “I SEE,” he said. The tone suggested that death was too good for cat haters.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="caturday" /><summary type="html">Favourite quotes Just a few of my favourite cat-related quotes from my favourite author. The late, great Sir Terry Pratchett. The cat wonderfully posing in the pictures is Sam. Sam actually lived 10 houses down from us. But decided to move in with his brother. We eventually found out where he lived. He moved back home, whilst his brother stayed with us. Honorable Mentions The Assassin moved quietly from roof to roof until he was well away from the excitement around the Watch House. His movements could be called cat-like, except that he did not stop to spray urine up against things. It’s an interesting fact that fewer than 17 % of Real cats end their lives with the same name they started with. Much family effort goes into selecting one at the start (“She looks like a Winnifred to me”), and then as the years roll by it suddenly finds itself being called Meepo or Ratbag. I hate cats.” Death’s face became a little stiffer, if that were possible. The blue glow in his eye sockets flickered red for an instant. “I SEE,” he said. The tone suggested that death was too good for cat haters.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">I’ve Tried Nothing And I’m All Out Of Ideas</title><link href="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/personal/2021/07/29/i-ve-tried-nothing-and-i-m-all-out-of-ideas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I’ve Tried Nothing And I’m All Out Of Ideas" /><published>2021-07-29T06:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-29T06:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://blog.thisispaddys.space/personal/2021/07/29/i-ve-tried-nothing-and-i-m-all-out-of-ideas</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/personal/2021/07/29/i-ve-tried-nothing-and-i-m-all-out-of-ideas/">&lt;p&gt;It’s been a month. Already? I know! Time flies when you’re having fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627508807/canva_assets/i_ve_tried_nothing_frqray.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of Pinterest pins claiming to double your page views. Help you start making \(\) in as revenue. Become Master of the Universe in 3 easy steps is ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never expected to make a penny from blogging. And so far my predictions have been correct. I have nothing to say. No pearls of wisdom. Nothing that hasn’t been said a thousand times before. And probably better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why do it? I’m not a social butterfly. I don’t know a ton of people. I’m shy, introverted, and quiet So why do I put myself out there?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;whats-my-niche-again&quot;&gt;what’s My Niche Again?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, really, why? I’d love to know because I’ll be buggered if I know! The online gurus say to find your niche. I have no idea if I have a niche.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I have depression.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I like animals (friends, not food).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I watch tennis.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’ve started to go to the gym (which is way, way out of my comfort zone)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I’ve tried learning Japanese but I have a terrible memory.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I fall in and out of interests.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I dwell on the negative instead of embracing the positive.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I barely know my own mind sometimes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1627506419/illustrations/4443395_p3lfqo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to play around with new things. New services. New websites. It distracts me from the real world. It’s the creation of something. It may be a boring old blog post that offers zero information or entertainment. But I guess it is just. Fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Playing around on canva creating crappy graphics. Signing up on form-building sites that nobody will fill out. Looking at pitiful analytics of visitor counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s all just fun. I like to make websites. Nobody will see them. Maybe that’s what I’m missing. I’m just doing this for enjoyment. Probably only me and my other half will ever read this and comment. Maybe my mum too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to go running. I’m never going to be an Olympic athlete. So why do it? Sheer enjoyment. Although with running it doesn’t usually feel like it at the time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an online world where everybody wants to be the best, earn the most. Get the most likes, page views, comments. Be noticed. I guess doing something for self-satisfaction feels a little strange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But maybe, that’s just me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh. So what have I learned?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well for one. I don’t need to quickly write a blog post, half-arse it, and say pretty much nothing interesting. Just to write ‘something’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also rather than being a small fish in a very big pond. I’m more of a speck of dust floating in the universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t expect to be even noticed. You may get a few visitors, who then quickly click to something more interesting.  Hell, I’ve done it myself. Clicked on something, read it, moved on. So I’m just as guilty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Write because you enjoy it. It’s therapeutic. Write for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re not going to make $$$ a month. You’ll be frustrated trying and lose the enjoyment of blogging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a pity post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More of, say, a reality check. A long rambling reality check that has a crappy ending.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="personal" /><summary type="html">It’s been a month. Already? I know! Time flies when you’re having fun. The number of Pinterest pins claiming to double your page views. Help you start making \(\) in as revenue. Become Master of the Universe in 3 easy steps is ridiculous. I never expected to make a penny from blogging. And so far my predictions have been correct. I have nothing to say. No pearls of wisdom. Nothing that hasn’t been said a thousand times before. And probably better. So why do it? I’m not a social butterfly. I don’t know a ton of people. I’m shy, introverted, and quiet So why do I put myself out there? what’s My Niche Again? No, really, why? I’d love to know because I’ll be buggered if I know! The online gurus say to find your niche. I have no idea if I have a niche. I have depression. I like animals (friends, not food). I watch tennis. I’ve started to go to the gym (which is way, way out of my comfort zone) I’ve tried learning Japanese but I have a terrible memory. I fall in and out of interests. I dwell on the negative instead of embracing the positive. I barely know my own mind sometimes. But. I like to play around with new things. New services. New websites. It distracts me from the real world. It’s the creation of something. It may be a boring old blog post that offers zero information or entertainment. But I guess it is just. Fun. Playing around on canva creating crappy graphics. Signing up on form-building sites that nobody will fill out. Looking at pitiful analytics of visitor counts. It’s all just fun. I like to make websites. Nobody will see them. Maybe that’s what I’m missing. I’m just doing this for enjoyment. Probably only me and my other half will ever read this and comment. Maybe my mum too. I like to go running. I’m never going to be an Olympic athlete. So why do it? Sheer enjoyment. Although with running it doesn’t usually feel like it at the time! In an online world where everybody wants to be the best, earn the most. Get the most likes, page views, comments. Be noticed. I guess doing something for self-satisfaction feels a little strange. But maybe, that’s just me. Oh. So what have I learned? Well for one. I don’t need to quickly write a blog post, half-arse it, and say pretty much nothing interesting. Just to write ‘something’ Also rather than being a small fish in a very big pond. I’m more of a speck of dust floating in the universe. Don’t expect to be even noticed. You may get a few visitors, who then quickly click to something more interesting. Hell, I’ve done it myself. Clicked on something, read it, moved on. So I’m just as guilty. Write because you enjoy it. It’s therapeutic. Write for yourself. You’re not going to make $$$ a month. You’ll be frustrated trying and lose the enjoyment of blogging. This isn’t a pity post. More of, say, a reality check. A long rambling reality check that has a crappy ending.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://blog.thisispaddys.space/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>