<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-GB"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en-GB" /><updated>2021-07-18T19:26:09+01:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blog.thisispaddys.space</title><subtitle>Home</subtitle><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><entry><title type="html">Quote of the Day</title><link href="/quotes/depression/2021/07/18/quote-of-the-day/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quote of the Day" /><published>2021-07-18T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-18T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/quotes/depression/2021/07/18/quote-of-the-day</id><content type="html" xml:base="/quotes/depression/2021/07/18/quote-of-the-day/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626598335/quotes/No_one_is_ever_happy_until_you_ve_taken_on_the_same_level_of_responsibility_they_are_unhappy_with_in_their_own_lives._wgbwmr.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The older I get, the more this sentence resonates with me. I don’t know if I’m just getting more cynical, jaded. If I’m just surrounded by such people that their negativity is rubbing off on me. If it’s world politics, events, or the pandemic. I just know there’s an overwhelming aura of despair that blankets my entire view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are moments of happiness that poke through the holes in this blanket. Little points of light shining through. But these don’t last long. Like coming up for air, flailing in the deep waters. These brief moments of sweet, fresh air are soon lost in the dark, unforgiving water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that’s enough terrible analogies that only a 15-year-old emo kid would be happy with. I’m 51, and the older I get the more these jaded thoughts are strengthened. Maybe I need to surround myself with more positive people. They must exist out there somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="quotes" /><category term="depression" /><summary type="html">The older I get, the more this sentence resonates with me. I don’t know if I’m just getting more cynical, jaded. If I’m just surrounded by such people that their negativity is rubbing off on me. If it’s world politics, events, or the pandemic. I just know there’s an overwhelming aura of despair that blankets my entire view. There are moments of happiness that poke through the holes in this blanket. Little points of light shining through. But these don’t last long. Like coming up for air, flailing in the deep waters. These brief moments of sweet, fresh air are soon lost in the dark, unforgiving water. I think that’s enough terrible analogies that only a 15-year-old emo kid would be happy with. I’m 51, and the older I get the more these jaded thoughts are strengthened. Maybe I need to surround myself with more positive people. They must exist out there somewhere.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">It’s Caturday</title><link href="/caturday/2021/07/17/it-s-caturday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It’s Caturday" /><published>2021-07-17T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-17T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/caturday/2021/07/17/it-s-caturday</id><content type="html" xml:base="/caturday/2021/07/17/it-s-caturday/">&lt;p&gt;When the weather gets this hot it’s best to just put your paws up and relax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/e_grayscale/v1626541620/blog/Caturday/paws_jswn1e.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="caturday" /><summary type="html">When the weather gets this hot it’s best to just put your paws up and relax.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">It’s Lead Work Wednesday #1</title><link href="/designs/2021/07/14/it-s-lead-work-wednesday-1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It’s Lead Work Wednesday #1" /><published>2021-07-14T06:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-14T06:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/designs/2021/07/14/it-s-lead-work-wednesday-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/designs/2021/07/14/it-s-lead-work-wednesday-1/">&lt;p&gt;The kind of work I love and hate. The customer wants birds, butterflies and flowers. And leaves the design up to me. I love getting free reign on designs. But the idea of it ALL being left up to me? including colours? Not so much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626276153/blog/work/IMG_20210630_142002_jiaktj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Initial sketch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few tweaks and layout changes to the design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626276156/blog/work/IMG_20210713_083625_oohurn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626276159/blog/work/IMG_20210714_093049_y2jqkv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then the leading begins! So far so good…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626276160/blog/work/IMG_20210714_133225_wg9guk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="designs" /><summary type="html">The kind of work I love and hate. The customer wants birds, butterflies and flowers. And leaves the design up to me. I love getting free reign on designs. But the idea of it ALL being left up to me? including colours? Not so much. A few tweaks and layout changes to the design. And then the leading begins! So far so good…</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Keep on running</title><link href="/running/c25k/2021/07/11/keep-on-running/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Keep on running" /><published>2021-07-11T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-11T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/running/c25k/2021/07/11/keep-on-running</id><content type="html" xml:base="/running/c25k/2021/07/11/keep-on-running/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1626000542/running/fitbitshare_11072021.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 3 - Run 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not getting any easier. I didn't think it would. I'd hoped. Trying to follow c25k is not easy when you only run once a week. Motivation is the killer. I am completely lacking in it. I _want _to do it. But this invisible forcefield keeps holding me back. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know one run a week is better than none. Just. But depression can be crippling first thing in the morning. The thought of another full day of stress, cats and the inability to want to do anything is strong. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weekdays I barely have the energy to get out of bed. Let alone go for a run! Weekends I just want to wallow in self pity. I'm sure the more I run the better I will feel. But getting over that first hurdle is challenging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, I feel good today. Getting that run out of the way has left me with a sense of achievement and aching legs. The good kind of ache. The ache you get from doing something.  I'm not sure I'll ever feel the full effects of a runners hight. And I don't know if I'll ever run for a full 5k.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as I keep trying then wherever I get to I have to view it as an achievement and not a failure.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="running" /><category term="c25k" /><summary type="html">Week 3 - Run 1 This is not getting any easier. I didn't think it would. I'd hoped. Trying to follow c25k is not easy when you only run once a week. Motivation is the killer. I am completely lacking in it. I _want _to do it. But this invisible forcefield keeps holding me back. I know one run a week is better than none. Just. But depression can be crippling first thing in the morning. The thought of another full day of stress, cats and the inability to want to do anything is strong. Weekdays I barely have the energy to get out of bed. Let alone go for a run! Weekends I just want to wallow in self pity. I'm sure the more I run the better I will feel. But getting over that first hurdle is challenging. But, I feel good today. Getting that run out of the way has left me with a sense of achievement and aching legs. The good kind of ache. The ache you get from doing something. I'm not sure I'll ever feel the full effects of a runners hight. And I don't know if I'll ever run for a full 5k. As long as I keep trying then wherever I get to I have to view it as an achievement and not a failure.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">It’s Caturday</title><link href="/caturday/2021/07/10/it-s-caturday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It’s Caturday" /><published>2021-07-10T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-10T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/caturday/2021/07/10/it-s-caturday</id><content type="html" xml:base="/caturday/2021/07/10/it-s-caturday/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1625928421/blog/Caturday/SleepyG.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Little G knows the relaxing benefits of a Caturday afternoon cat nap&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="caturday" /><summary type="html">Little G knows the relaxing benefits of a Caturday afternoon cat nap</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Why am I doing this?</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/08/why-am-i-doing-this/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why am I doing this?" /><published>2021-07-08T01:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-08T01:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/08/why-am-i-doing-this</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/08/why-am-i-doing-this/">&lt;p&gt;I’m a nobody. I guess we all are at some point in our lives. Maybe. Or maybe it’s just me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m on all the usual social media sites under a different username. Got a few acquaintances and people that could be called friends following me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why have I hit the reset button? Started from scratch. Where nobody will read this. Nobody will follow me. I’m not a social person by nature. I don’t have any words of wisdom or skills to offer the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A fifty something&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vegan (non pushy)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;With depression&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Someone who likes the idea of friends. But doesn’t like people.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why the hell would I want to attract people to read my very inarticulate blog, look at my mundane pictures or talk to a depressing introvert?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I’m trying to find myself again. I used to have a blogger blog back in the dark ages, and a livejournal and a Tumblr. I recently migrated my old blogger posts to this blog. It was interesting going over them again. Like finding an old diary. I enjoyed being on blogger until I didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I just need this right now. A fresh start. Just a new me on the internet. Where nobody knows me. And maybe nobody will want to know me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I’m ok with that.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">I’m a nobody. I guess we all are at some point in our lives. Maybe. Or maybe it’s just me. I’m on all the usual social media sites under a different username. Got a few acquaintances and people that could be called friends following me. So why have I hit the reset button? Started from scratch. Where nobody will read this. Nobody will follow me. I’m not a social person by nature. I don’t have any words of wisdom or skills to offer the world. I’m A fifty something Vegan (non pushy) With depression Someone who likes the idea of friends. But doesn’t like people. So why the hell would I want to attract people to read my very inarticulate blog, look at my mundane pictures or talk to a depressing introvert? I think I’m trying to find myself again. I used to have a blogger blog back in the dark ages, and a livejournal and a Tumblr. I recently migrated my old blogger posts to this blog. It was interesting going over them again. Like finding an old diary. I enjoyed being on blogger until I didn’t. Maybe I just need this right now. A fresh start. Just a new me on the internet. Where nobody knows me. And maybe nobody will want to know me. And I’m ok with that.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A day in my life</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/06/i-hate-time/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A day in my life" /><published>2021-07-06T02:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-06T02:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/06/i-hate-time</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/06/i-hate-time/">&lt;p&gt;3 am Little G wakes me up to go out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6 am My alarm goes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:10 am my alarm goes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:20 am my alarm goes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:30 am my alarm goes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7-8 am I try and survive the morning cat feed, preparing my lunch, getting breakfast. And make a half hearted attempt to be ready and at work for 8 am&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:10 am arrive at work&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:10 am-4:30 pm spend the day in my own pit of hell having to work with some of the dumbest people I have ever had the misfortune of meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4:30-8:30 pm This could go either way. Depending on the kind of day Zara has had will dictate everything, from the mood of the cats to affecting every ounce of my being. Watch tv, eat dinner, feed cats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8:30-10 pm This will be stressful regardless. Getting cats sorted, fed, and happy whilst we bicker about everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10-12pm Bed. Peace. Quiet. The time I can do what I want, watch what I want. The world has gone to sleep. The world is silent. I should be going to sleep. Getting rest to repeat the whole process all over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I feel my time is wasted being asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I sleep it will be tomorrow even quicker.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">3 am Little G wakes me up to go out. 6 am My alarm goes off. 6:10 am my alarm goes off. 6:20 am my alarm goes off. 6:30 am my alarm goes off. 7-8 am I try and survive the morning cat feed, preparing my lunch, getting breakfast. And make a half hearted attempt to be ready and at work for 8 am 8:10 am arrive at work 8:10 am-4:30 pm spend the day in my own pit of hell having to work with some of the dumbest people I have ever had the misfortune of meeting. 4:30-8:30 pm This could go either way. Depending on the kind of day Zara has had will dictate everything, from the mood of the cats to affecting every ounce of my being. Watch tv, eat dinner, feed cats. 8:30-10 pm This will be stressful regardless. Getting cats sorted, fed, and happy whilst we bicker about everything. 10-12pm Bed. Peace. Quiet. The time I can do what I want, watch what I want. The world has gone to sleep. The world is silent. I should be going to sleep. Getting rest to repeat the whole process all over again. But I feel my time is wasted being asleep. If I sleep it will be tomorrow even quicker.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">I don’t like Mondays</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/05/i-don-t-like-mondays/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I don’t like Mondays" /><published>2021-07-05T07:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-05T07:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/05/i-don-t-like-mondays</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/05/i-don-t-like-mondays/">&lt;p&gt;It’s that feeling of “here we go again” We’re at the top of the rollercoaster. Just bracing for the sudden stomach-churning descent. Which is great if you like the exhilaration of the ride. I’ve always hated rollercoasters. Never been on one. Never wanted to. Never will. Rollercoasters are like life. I never asked to be on the damn thing. But here I am, going through the same stomach-churning experience. Round and round. Up and down. Feeling sicker and sicker as time goes by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to get off. But I’m stuck on this damn thing because everybody I love is here with me. Going through various feelings of exhilaration and nausea of their own. And feeling like, “well, they’re here with me so I’d better stay on the ride”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do sometimes enjoy it. When it’s going slow, at the bottom where it feels like it’s virtually stopped. The calm before the storm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yeah. I don’t like Mondays. Or rollercoasters.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">It’s that feeling of “here we go again” We’re at the top of the rollercoaster. Just bracing for the sudden stomach-churning descent. Which is great if you like the exhilaration of the ride. I’ve always hated rollercoasters. Never been on one. Never wanted to. Never will. Rollercoasters are like life. I never asked to be on the damn thing. But here I am, going through the same stomach-churning experience. Round and round. Up and down. Feeling sicker and sicker as time goes by. I want to get off. But I’m stuck on this damn thing because everybody I love is here with me. Going through various feelings of exhilaration and nausea of their own. And feeling like, “well, they’re here with me so I’d better stay on the ride” I do sometimes enjoy it. When it’s going slow, at the bottom where it feels like it’s virtually stopped. The calm before the storm. So yeah. I don’t like Mondays. Or rollercoasters.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">It’s Caturday</title><link href="/caturday/2021/07/03/its-caturday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="It’s Caturday" /><published>2021-07-03T06:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-03T06:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/caturday/2021/07/03/its-caturday</id><content type="html" xml:base="/caturday/2021/07/03/its-caturday/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/e_oil_paint:25/v1625262596/blog/hzwjmcjg1c7zc4lga1vr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Caturday" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The testing is over</title><link href="/personal/2021/07/01/the-testing-is-over/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The testing is over" /><published>2021-07-01T04:01:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-07-01T04:01:00+01:00</updated><id>/personal/2021/07/01/the-testing-is-over</id><content type="html" xml:base="/personal/2021/07/01/the-testing-is-over/">&lt;p&gt;Well. Here I go. A blog about my thoughts and ideas. I don’t have many thoughts. Or ideas. I feel like I just float through life being buffeted by whatever comes my way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember being asked by the careers counselor at school what I wanted to be in life. I didn’t have a clue. I was a suicidal 15 year old so I just said I wanted to be happy. I was asked again when I was at college.  &lt;!-- more --&gt; now a suicidal 17 year old. I still didn’t know. I didn’t know at 20, 30 or 40. I’m now 51 and I still don’t know. Nor do I care now. I’ve sailed through life without any goal or vision. I’ve seen people i love die before their time. I’ve seen relationships crumble and dreams shatter. So I just keep floating through life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/paddysplace/image/upload/v1625159510/blog/undraw_career_progress_ivdb_vk9nxw.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; title=&quot;Career progress&quot; /&gt;I’ve made half hearted attempts at life. I’ve had moments where things seemed to be going well_._ But they fade away eventually. I’ve been good, bad, selfish, selfless and on occasions illegal. But nothing seems to stick. I’ve thrown myself into interests 110% but eventually the bubble bursts and I’m looking for the next hook. The next thing I can cling onto in the hope it can catapult me through the rest of my life. It’s a lot to ask of something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all sounds so pointless as a life. We’ve only got one life so live it. So they say. But it’s like being given a book and told to read it. And enjoy it. It’s the only book you’re ever going to have. So make the most of it. So you slog your way through page after page of mundane story. Just hoping you can get through it quickly. To get to the end and breathe your last sigh of relief that it’s finally over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The end.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>paddyplace</name></author><category term="Personal" /><summary type="html">Well. Here I go. A blog about my thoughts and ideas. I don’t have many thoughts. Or ideas. I feel like I just float through life being buffeted by whatever comes my way. I remember being asked by the careers counselor at school what I wanted to be in life. I didn’t have a clue. I was a suicidal 15 year old so I just said I wanted to be happy. I was asked again when I was at college.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/default-social-image.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>